# **Damon Rocha**



dmarcr1997@gmail.com



9038183759



linkedin.com/in/dmr4414

### **Summary**

My name is Damon Rocha and I am a tenacious programmer. I started coding C++ in college. I must have liked it or something because I then changed my degree plan to computer science, and on completion of my degree, I decided to go to a Flatiron to hone my craft. I am now experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript-based programming with a background in C++ and Python. Due to the amount of math, I took in college I have a detailed Math, Calculus, and Physics background centered around electronics and science. And to wrap it all up I possess strong skills in team-building and project management that I gained in working with UPS and as a supervisor at Kohls.

### **Experience**



### Developer

Vanguard Nov 2020 - Present (3 months +) Open Account developer

### 爾 Seasonal Package Loader

**UPS** 

Jul 2018 - Mar 2019 (9 months)

## конеѕ

#### **Home and Kids Supervisor**

Kohl's

Apr 2017 - Jul 2018 (1 year 4 months)

#### **Education**



#### Flatiron School

Computer Software Engineering 2020 - 2020 Online Software Engineering Bootcamp

### **Grayson College**

Associate of Science- AS, Computer Science

2017 - 2019

oPut on Dean's list Summer 2017

Place on Presidents List for a GPA of 4.0 in the Fall of 2018

Awarded Outstanding Computer Science Student award spring of 2020

Finished three programming classes in C++ and a Computer Assembly course

Earned an A in a technical writing class, Calculus 3 and University Physics 1 & 2

### **Skills**

Mathematics • Software Development • Python (Programming Language) • Computer Science • JavaScript • Team Building • Project Management • Angular • Physics • Electrical Engineering